<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CogSci Productions on </title>
    <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/cogsci-productions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CogSci Productions on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://cogsci.dk/docs/cogsci-productions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications by students</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/cogsci-productions/student-publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/cogsci-productions/student-publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications by students Analysing political biases in danish newspapers using sentiment analysis Link
By Kenneth C Enevoldsen, Lasse Hansen
2017
Language-Works
Traditionally, the evaluation of political biases in Danish newspapers has been carried out through highly subjective methods. The conventional approach has been surveys asking samples of the population to place various newspapers on the political spectrum, coupled with analysing voting habits of the newspapers’ readers (Hjarvard, 2007). This paper seeks to examine whether it is possible to use sentiment analysis to objectively assess political biases in Danish newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CogTalks</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/cogsci-productions/cogtalks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/cogsci-productions/cogtalks/</guid>
      <description>Cog Productions CogTalks Social Compliance during Covid-19 with Lasse Hyldig Hansen Neuroimaging &amp;amp; Machine Learning with Esben Kran Experience Engineering with Aleksandrs Baskakovs Emotions with Sebastian Scott Engen When Reality Breaks (Brain Anomalies) with Lasse D. Elholm Making Safe AI with Cognitive Science and with Jonathan H. Rystrøm Escaping the AI Chasm with Malte Højmark-Bertelsen Vocal Markers in ASD and Schizophrenia with Riccardo Fusaroli Cognitive Semiotics and Neuroscience with Jannik Wiggers Disinformation &amp;amp; Democracies with Maris Sala Explainable AI &amp;amp; Cognitive Science with Millie Søndergaard Computational Modeling of Gambling Decisions with Simon Hansen Code Optimization in R with Lasse Letager Hansen Quest into Uncertainty with Savhannah Schulz Radiators &amp;amp; Communication with Mikkel Wallentin Industry Adventures with Jonathan H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exam Projects</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/cogsci-productions/exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/cogsci-productions/exams/</guid>
      <description>Earlier exam projects Cognition &amp;amp; Communication Anders &amp;amp; Laurits Arnold &amp;amp; AnnaMaya Kathrine &amp;amp; Frederikke Lasse &amp;amp; Pernille Lisa &amp;amp; Line Mikkel &amp;amp; Carl Sebastian &amp;amp; Nina Thea, Signe &amp;amp; Kiri </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Productions</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/cogsci-productions/other-productions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/cogsci-productions/other-productions/</guid>
      <description> Student packages and models Ludvig&amp;rsquo;s R packages: groupdata2 cvms xpectr rearrr Peter and Kenneth&amp;rsquo;s Tomsup theory of mind simulation Kenneth&amp;rsquo;s DaCy Danish language model Gustav and Jakob&amp;rsquo;s Sentida Danish sentiment tool Malte&amp;rsquo;s Ælæctra model Student apps Sofie and Astrid&amp;rsquo;s NLP for Humanities learning app Seb and Esben&amp;rsquo;s beta for an ideas page Student misc. Lasse&amp;rsquo;s fantastic card game CogFight Lasse and Lasse&amp;rsquo;s Cognitive Disorder Atlas poster Esben&amp;rsquo;s depressed flower game Cool games Universal Paperclips Game Can&amp;rsquo;t Unsee </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
