<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contribute on </title>
    <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/contribute/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contribute on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://cogsci.dk/docs/contribute/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adding content</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/contribute/adding-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/contribute/adding-content/</guid>
      <description>Adding content First, you have to fork the repository as shown in this guide.
Adding to lists If you want to add to a list on the website, note how that list is currently set up and copy the elements to make your addition adhere to the current formatting.
For many of the lists, a specific shortcode is important. This shortcode is the ` ` shortcode. It is structured as shown below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/contribute/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/contribute/markdown/</guid>
      <description>Writing in markdown Software basics One of the absolute best ways to write markdown files is to use Visual Studio Code and install the Markdown All in One plugin that adds highlighting and assistive features when you&amp;rsquo;re editing a .md file. This is extremely useful. Some usage examples are shown on the link.
Text basics Writing text and clicking enter to get to the next line just continues your current line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing a blog post</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/contribute/writing-a-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/contribute/writing-a-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>Writing a blog post File and folder setup You write a .md file which stands for .markdown. Markdown is an established way to write with formatting. You can find instructions on how to write it on this page.
The name of the file has to be in the following syntax: **my-blog-post.md with dashes instead of spaces and in all lower-case. This ensures that we can link between pages optimally.
By following this guide, you have access to the file structure of the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My title</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/contribute/example-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/contribute/example-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>Example blog post Instruction Above are two different sizes of headings based on the amount of pound (#) signs. See the instructions for an extensive guide on writing a blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
