<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Extended learning on </title>
    <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Extended learning on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning platforms</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/platforms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/platforms/</guid>
      <description>Online Learning Platforms Coursera Take an extra degree with an online course.
https://www.coursera.org/
Codeacademy Learn to code
https://www.codecademy.com
MIT MIT OpenCourseware - Take An MIT course online
https://ocw.mit.edu/index.htm
EDX Take an extra degree with an online course
https://www.edx.org/
Udacity Nanodegrees https://eu.udacity.com/
Udemy Take an extra degree with an online course
https://www.udemy.com/
Brilliant Brilliant Bite-sized courses for STEM topics
https://brilliant.org/
Spinning Up An educational resource that makes it easier to learn about deep reinforcement learning (deep RL)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online courses</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/online-courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/online-courses/</guid>
      <description>Online Courses Database Curated by Aarhus University, Cognitive Science, Esben Kran and Sebastian Engen
This contains a list of many online courses. Originally curated for preliminary approval of courses outside Aarhus University (this is not possible for many of them). See a complete list of the content below. You are welcome to add an online course to the list according to the current structure. Try to ensure the quality of the course (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/books/</guid>
      <description>Books Meta Sites Archive - Online Archive of almost anything you could imagine link
Gutenberg - Non-profit digital library offering millions of free public domain books (Almost all the classics) link
LibriVox - Non-profit digital volunteer-run initiative that aims to release public domain audiobooks. Meta Books R for data scientists - This book will teach you how to do data science with R link
A Language, not a Letter: Learning Statistics in R link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Podcast recommendations Student Recommendations Luke Ring Brain-Related Brain Science with Ginger Campbell
Interesting topics and some amazing guests. Also I once emailed the host for clarification and she took the time to reply and was just very nice.
Tech Darknet Diaries
Hands down the best made podcast on cyber security. Episodes are well produced and have a storytelling narrative that is engaging and entertaining, often interviewees are hackers, criminals, and security professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interesting videos</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/video-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/video-talks/</guid>
      <description>#Language Video Lectures BOLD TITLE one-liner explanation link
BOLD TITLE one-liner explanation link
Video Tutorials BOLD TITLE one-liner explanation link
BOLD TITLE one-liner explanation link
Podcasts title link
title link
#Emotion
Language Steven Pinker: What Our Language Habits Reveal Psycholinguist Steven Pinker talks about how language both transmits information and reflects social relations.
https://www.ted.com/talks/steven_pinker_what_our_language_habits_reveal/up-next?language=en
Lera Boroditsky: How Language Shapes the Way We Think Cognitive linguist Lera Boroditsky talks about the influence of our language on our mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video tutorials</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/video-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/learning/video-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>UNSORTED The Chinese Room Experiment (BBC) Mary’s Room Thought Experiment Crash Course: Action potential Crash Course: Synapses Crash Course: Vision 2-Minute Neuroscience: Membrane potential 2-Minute Neuroscience: Action Potential 2-Minute Neuroscience: Synaptic transmission 2-Minute Neuroscience: Release of neurotransmitters 2-Minute Neuroscience: Vision Psychopy: Build Your First Experiment 3Blue1Brown. Neural Networks https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLZHQObOWTQDNU6R1_67000Dx_ZCJB-3pi </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
