<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Example Site on </title>
    <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/hidden/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Example Site on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://cogsci.dk/docs/hidden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Study Café</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/hidden/study-cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/hidden/study-cafe/</guid>
      <description>Study Café </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutor list</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/hidden/tutor-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/hidden/tutor-list/</guid>
      <description>Tutor list This is an assembly of people who find it fun to help out with Statistics, Coding, Designing Experiments &amp;amp; Data Visualisation Here you can get in contact with knowledgeful Cognitive Science Students if you need help with your work. It might be for shorter consultations or for help with larger projects where you&amp;rsquo;d like to pay someone for assisting you with all the nitty-gritty details. Moreover, I&amp;rsquo;ve also been asked by other students to be their private tutor and this could also be a place to find such a friend :) Sign-Up below or look through the list to find yourself a tutor, programmer, statistician, web-designer or any other type of PC Pirate Sebastian Scott Engen Qualifications R and python: Data Visualisation, Statistical Modelling, Experiment design+implementation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/hidden/hidden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/hidden/hidden/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: In general, the academic level (e.g. statistical abilities) of the papers should be expected to increase by semester. The current state-of-the-art (SOTA) model of this is goodness ~ semester + num_broca_parties * num_lockdowns + (1|year) (10-fold repeated cross-validation). This disclaimer is not meant to degrade papers from earlier semesters (that are most likely awesome (our model has a high intercept)) but just an honest note that we all get drastically better with time, and we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be afraid of sharing our imperfect work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
