<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Hub on </title>
    <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/social/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Hub on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://cogsci.dk/docs/social/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Teacher list</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/social/all-teachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/social/all-teachers/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor 1st Semester Kristian Tylén (Teacher in Cognition &amp;amp; Communication) Sebastian Scott Engen (Student Instructor in Cognition &amp;amp; Communication) Fabio Trecca (Teacher in Methods 1) Jonathan Hvithamar Rystrøm (Student Instructor in Methods 1) Daina Crafa (Teacher in Introduction to Cognitive Science) Anders Weile Larsen (Student Instructor in Introduction to Cognitive Science) 3rd Semester Byurakn Ishkhanyan (Teacher in Methods 3) Victor Poulsen (Student Instructor in Methods 3) Daina Crafa (Teacher in Mind &amp;amp; Conciousness) Master 1st Semester Chris Mathys (Teacher in Deciosionmaking) Rebekah Brita Baglini (Teacher in Natural Language Processing) Mads Jensen (Teacher in Advanced Cognitive Neuroscience) Aarhus University Cognitive Science Staff Joshua Charles Skewes (Head of Department at Linguistics, Cognitive Science and Semiotics) Blanka Sara Palfi (Instructor of Study Techniques) Sofie Nødskov Ditmer Sørensen (Student Instructor) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AU environment</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/social/au-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/social/au-environment/</guid>
      <description>The Environment at Aarhus University Aarhus University&amp;rsquo;s Entrepreneurial Incubator The Kitchen At The Kitchen, they support students who want to work on entrepreneurial projects while studying. Some of their activities are in Danish, but if you are an AU-student and you have a business idea, they will be happy to help you move it forward. Link Research groups Crafa Lab Her research investigates the effects of culture and social contexts on human development, brain processes, and genetics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social groups</title>
      <link>https://cogsci.dk/docs/social/social-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cogsci.dk/docs/social/social-groups/</guid>
      <description>Social Groups CogChess We do cogs on chess boards! Join us please! Pleease?
FB Contact: https://www.facebook.com/anders.haagerup
FB group: https://www.facebook.com/groups/347525079305702/
CogClimbers We climb on cogs as true heroes! We have enough cogs to climb but feel free to join!
FB Contact: https://www.facebook.com/danielelmstom
FB group: https://www.facebook.com/groups/2092521237743477/
CogKnition FB Contact: https://www.facebook.com/sigrid.a.nielsen
FB group: https://www.facebook.com/groups/713170942483009/
Cogs who squat (a lot) We squat. That&amp;rsquo;s what we do! DEAL WITH IT!
FB Contact: https://www.facebook.com/julie.s.nielsen
FB group: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
